[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 31]
[Tiecheng Construction]
Tell He to unload
the materials at the square. Hurry up.
Send someone to keep a close eye on it.
Got it.
Alright.
How's the demolition going
in the Siying Road neighborhood?
Working on it.
It's still early.
Maybe it'll change in a couple of days.
What are you doing?
Don't get physical.
This is our Zhao family's house!
Exactly.
Why are you outsiders fighting over this?
Who do you think you are?
Bah! Have you no shame?
In the years before the old lady died,
none of you ever showed up.
Nonsense!
Our Changyou had been looking after her.
The old lady said
this house goes to us.
Exactly.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
You're talking crap!
How long has your Changyou been dead?
Why are you only finding out now?
Alright.
Stop arguing.
-The police are here.
-Let go of your hands. Come on.
Officer.
You're here.
You tell her.
If this house had nothing to do with us,
how would you have found us, right?
-It must be ours.
-These are all Zhao Changyou's relatives.
It seems
there's something wrong with this house.
Is it your house?
Why should he open it for you?
150. Open it for me.
Don't listen to her.
I'll give 200.
Whoever pays—
200! 250!
Listen to me.
Open it for me!
Open it for us!
Whoever pays,
isn't it the same door being opened?
What are you fighting over?
Making such a fuss!
Listen to me.
Once the door is opened,
you all wait outside.
The stuff inside
might be involved in a case.
Once we've investigated thoroughly,
we'll resolve your issue.
Do you hear me?
Come on, come out.
Come out in an orderly way. Come on.
Stop fighting.
You don't even have the property deed,
and you still want to occupy our house?
Come on, open the door.
If the stuff inside
is really related to the case,
we need to keep a close eye on it.
Watch it.
Don't worry, Juan.
Flashlight.
What's this smell?
Hello? Who are you looking for?
He Liang, it's for you.
Hello?
Juan?
Ma, take a look at this file.
Liang?
-When did you come back?
-Liang.
-Give it to me.
-Why are you back?
Thank you.
Liang's back.
First time seeing you in a police uniform.
It fits you perfectly.
Yeah.
Liang, what treats
did you bring this time?
I'm treating you guys to dinner tonight.
Liang, how long
are you planning to stay this time?
That depends on how the case goes.
You should just transfer to Tiecheng.
-Yeah.
I'll follow orders.
I haven't finished
sorting the Siying Road files yet.
Give me a hand.
Sure.
Come on.
Right.
What?
I helped you solve such a big case.
And you just bought me
a bag of sunflower seeds?
I was in a hurry.
I hung up your call
and bought a ticket right away.
What are you standing there for?
We only found out
when we contacted them for demolition.
The old lady has been dead for years.
The house was never transferred.
None of her immediate
family members could be reached.
Instead, all those distant relatives
popped up.
That's when we found out
she had a grandson—
that Zhao Changyou
who froze to death last year.
How did the dance hall owner
die in the room?
Isn't that what
you're supposed to find out?
Let me tell you.
That guy was really strong.
He was stuffed
in the freezer for who knows how long.
The meat was all frozen and rotten.
It took a lot of effort to get it out.
They had to scoop
the meat out spoon by spoon.
That smell...
It was like pig offal.
Okay.
I'll read the report myself later.
Is the on-site investigation over?
No.
We notified you
as soon as we got the report.
We're regular police.
We can only assist in solving the case.
The precinct sent
detectives and forensics.
They've collected evidence.
But this case is still yours.
We have to follow your lead.
My colleague will arrive tomorrow.
I'll go check out
the scene this afternoon.
You feel like eating?
There's a place over there
that makes great blood sausage.
If you don't eat now, it'll be demolished.
I'll skip it.
Where's Qianqian?
How come I didn't see her just now?
She's at kindergarten.
I can't bring her to work every day.
No wonder
she hasn't called me lately.
What,
you want to learn
Cantonese from her again?
Juan.
Can I still stay
at your place for this business trip?
Come on, Director.
Don't fake being drunk. Drink up.
Yeah.
Who's faking?
Come on.
Drink.
Bottoms up.
We're watching.
No leftovers.
Hey, Luo,
you two, stop being
all lovey-dovey over there, okay?
Exactly.
Don't think I can't tell.
You two better take your glasses
and come to the two bosses here
to give a report, okay?
Stop it.
Report what?
Since when?
What?
Wang Hailong.
You two—how did I not see it?
Congratulations to you both.
Thank you.
-Cheers!
Be good together.
Well...
Mr. Liu, Ms. Chen,
I'd like to say something bold on this
happy occasion.
Listen up.
You two—
you've even had a child now.
When are you going to make it official?
Right?
Yeah!
Did I...
Did I say something wrong?
Well,
I...
I'll take a penalty drink.
Penalty drink.
Take a penalty drink.
Well,
let me propose a toast.
Juan.
I can't drink.
I'll have a beverage.
Okay.
Liu Yang.
It's been hard for you.
It's what I should do.
Well,
first, I wish the child
a healthy growth.
Thank you.
Mrs. Liu.
Mrs. Liu?
Mrs. Liu, huh?
Well, then they are family now.
Right?
I wish you a prosperous
life together.
Thank you.
How about a cross-cupped toast?
Cross-cupped!
Come on.
Cheers.
I have to say,
the sister-in-law is the best.
Yeah.
Straightforward.
Let's all raise our glasses!
Cheers!
Cheers.
Yes, let's have another toast.
I'll go over there for a bit.
Qiu, are you full?
I'm full.
-Are you?
-Mom, I'm so bored.
Then go play outside.
There are fish over there.
Ms. Liu.
You and Grandma take him
to watch the fish outside.
-Let's go watch the fish.
-Be careful.
Okay.
Back then, you thought I was easy
to control since I came from a small town.
You took advantage of
my parents' illness and need for money
and forced me to marry your son.
After I married him,
how did he treat me?
You and the old lady know very well.
Whatever the consequences,
you have to bear them.
You started it.
This is karma.
Accept your fate.
Maybe you'll live a couple more years.
Still sleeping.
It's fine.
Drink less.
Look, your face is red.
I'm fine.
Alright.
Drink less.
Why do they keep toasting?
Hello, pager 9638.
The restaurant opens today.
Remember to come and eat fried pork.
[People's Fast Food]
Thank you all for
coming to our little restaurant.
That's it for today.
Just enjoy yourselves, okay?
Okay!
[Good Friends Home Cooking]
Come on!
Pager 9638.
I forgot to tell you the address.
It's right behind the old hair salon.
Enjoy your meal. Take your time.
Pager 9638.
Coming right up.
Hao Peng, are you coming or not?
Pager 9638.
Really good.
I figure you're off
running around the world again.
When you return to Tiecheng,
don't forget to come and eat fried pork.
I named the place
[Good Friends Home Cooking]
"Good Friends Home Cooking."
It means Hao Peng has a home.
From now on,
just treat this place as your home.
[Archives Room]
Juan.
I saw you downstairs just now.
I thought it was you.
[Archives Room]
I have good news for you.
You've done a great job this time.
The chief even said
he wants to transfer you back.
Really?
Really.
The old man finally figured it out.
Don't tell anyone I said that.
I won't.
Have some seeds.
Thank you.
Well, Juan.
I'll get back to work.
Go ahead.
Okay.
[Chief's Office]
Okay. According to the list,
call all these people back
for questioning.
That Liu Yang—call him back too.
Okay.
Which Liu Yang?
Does my brother
have anything to do with this case?
Juan.
Take a look. Do you know this person?
Isn't this Three Eyes?
His real name is Hao Peng.
Earlier we found
a business card at the scene.
It was his.
Later, we found cigarette butts.
After forensic analysis,
we found they were also his.
We also found his footprints at the scene.
I've always called him by his nickname.
I forgot his real name.
Here's the thing.
We now suspect that
Liang Zhendong
had long been buying wild animals
from Zhao Changyou.
And Hao Peng
used smuggled cigarette sales as a cover,
but he's actually helping Liang Zhendong
distribute them there.
And Zhao Changyou's death
is very likely related to both of them.
Maybe this Zhao Changyou
spilled the warehouse address
after drinking.
Those two got greedy.
Then for some reason they had a dispute,
and Hao Peng killed Liang Zhendong.
The body was hidden
in the freezer at that warehouse.
That can't be.
I've known
Three Eyes for years.
He's an honest kid,
and not too bright.
He can't even count to twenty
without taking off his socks.
No matter how reckless Liang Zhendong was,
he wouldn't team up
with an idiot.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
Maybe he's just too smart
and fooled everyone.
But,
this is all just speculation based on
the current evidence.
Then where is Three Eyes now?
We haven't found him yet.
That's why
we're calling all the relevant people back
for questioning.
I'll go ask my brother.
Juan,
you have to recuse yourself.
We'll ask him.
Okay.
When was the last time you saw Three Eyes?
[Welcome]
It's been a while.
I can't remember how long.
About a week.
Have you seen this knife?
No wonder he stopped us from calling
the police when Dong went missing.
Three Eyes.
This knife is his!
He's the one who killed Dong!
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible, officer.
You must be mistaken.
Hao Peng is a really good guy.
He never gets handsy
when he comes to my salon.
Every time he just
gets a wash and a haircut.
Last time he came back from Guangzhou,
he brought me a bottle of hand cream.
He said he'd come to eat fried pork
when my little restaurant opens.
But I've paged him several times
and he never got back to me.
I'm worried something happened to him.
At first,
I hadn't seen this guy.
Just speak normally.
I just knew recently
he was selling cigarettes for Dong.
After Dong went missing,
he got a group of people
to renovate the dance hall.
It looks like a veteran cadre center now.
[Hao Peng, Golden Imperial Dance Hall]
And he said it was Dong's idea.
When was the last time you saw Hao Peng?
Does he have
any close friends?
Have you heard of Siying Road?
I felt something was wrong early on.